KEVIN OWIDI, SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Nakuru, Kenya, 0791381653, kevinalex846@qmail.com

LINKS

Github LinkedIn

PROFILE

I am a software developer with 3 years experience in a variety of programming languages and development frameworks. I have a strong background in object-oriented programming and have experience working on large-scale applications. I am also familiar with a variety of software development tools and have a good understanding of the software development process.

EXPERIENCE

Self / Freelance Developer

Feb. 2019 - PRESENT. Nakuru

Was responsible for designing, developing, testing and deploying web and mobile applications for both individual clients and teams within and outside the country. This has helped gain insights on how to work collaboratively with teams and also on how to efficiently elicit user requirements for better end products.

Self / Meal-IO Backend

Jul, 2022 - Nov, 2022, Nakuru

Developed a full operational back-end server with a well documented API interface to serve my client mobile and web app. This server simulates the operations that take place in a real world food order and delivery system with major functionalities such as Authentication, Product browsing and filtration, Cart and checkout applications.

Link: https://github.com/owidi-001/green veges backend

Self / Meal-IO Client App

Jul, 2022 - Nov, 2022, Nakuru

Developed a cross platform mobile application that simulates the real world food ordering and delivery application with user based focused on the customer. The application is developed using flutter.

Link: https://github.com/owidi-001/green_veges

Self / Meal-IO Rider(M-rider)

Nov, 2022 - Nov, 2022, Nakuru

Developed a rider application for the food order and delivery application where it simulates the order requests and order detail confirmation functionalities.

Link: https://github.com/owidi-001/meal-io-rider

EDUCATION

Egerton University/ Bsc. Computer Science

Sep, 2018 - Present, Nakuru

In my final year pursuing bachelors of Science in Computer Science.

Kisumu High School / KCSE

Jan, 2014 - Dec, 2017, Kisumu

Successfully completed my Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education at this institution.

CORE SKILLS

Flutter

Python

Django

SQL

Git

REFERENCE

Dr. Zachary Bosire, COD Egerton University

eribosire@gmail.com . 0729154296

Dr. Phoebe Ongalo, Egerton University

pheobe.ongalo@egerton.ac.ke . 0738300218